{
  "math_1_Questions": [
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 9?", "answers": ["12", "13", "14", "15"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 4?", "answers": ["20", "19", "9", "10"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 5?", "answers": ["20", "12", "9", "11"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 - 1?", "answers": ["12", "7", "14", "1"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 - 2?", "answers": ["16", "17", "19", "2"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 7?", "answers": ["14", "17", "15", "9"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 - 1?", "answers": ["17", "0", "1", "10"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 3?", "answers": ["7", "2", "13", "12"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 - 1?", "answers": ["7", "5", "4", "0"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 4?", "answers": ["14", "1", "13", "5"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 5?", "answers": ["10", "2", "15", "0"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 + 8?", "answers": ["10", "4", "12", "18"], "correctAnswer": "18" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 + 6?", "answers": ["15", "16", "6", "10"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 9 - 4?", "answers": ["10", "4", "5", "20"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 5?", "answers": ["15", "16", "0", "20"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 3?", "answers": ["9", "15", "10", "17"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 9?", "answers": ["17", "2", "19", "15"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 - 1?", "answers": ["4", "7", "0", "13"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 2?", "answers": ["1", "4", "20", "16"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 1?", "answers": ["14", "13", "5", "7"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 2?", "answers": ["17", "19", "5", "20"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 6?", "answers": ["12", "11", "2", "8"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 - 1?", "answers": ["0", "13", "17", "2"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 6?", "answers": ["12", "4", "14", "20"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 - 1?", "answers": ["8", "0", "14", "3"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 3?", "answers": ["18", "5", "7", "4"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 4?", "answers": ["2", "17", "9", "1"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 6?", "answers": ["5", "20", "10", "8"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 10?", "answers": ["5", "17", "2", "12"], "correctAnswer": "17" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 7?", "answers": ["1", "3", "9", "18"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 - 4?", "answers": ["0", "6", "5", "18"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 2?", "answers": ["10", "5", "15", "4"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 6?", "answers": ["12", "15", "20", "0"], "correctAnswer": "0" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 6?", "answers": ["13", "14", "4", "6"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 3?", "answers": ["11", "17", "16", "18"], "correctAnswer": "11" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 4?", "answers": ["18", "5", "7", "3"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 10?", "answers": ["15", "12", "1", "5"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 3?", "answers": ["7", "1", "19", "5"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 1?", "answers": ["1", "2", "14", "9"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 2?", "answers": ["17", "3", "7", "20"], "correctAnswer": "7" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 6?", "answers": ["6", "8", "5", "15"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 9?", "answers": ["16", "3", "20", "17"], "correctAnswer": "16" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 - 1?", "answers": ["1", "11", "20", "18"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 7?", "answers": ["19", "4", "9", "2"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 + 5?", "answers": ["7", "6", "8", "9"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 7?", "answers": ["10", "11", "13", "12"], "correctAnswer": "13" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 - 4?", "answers": ["6", "5", "4", "3"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 2?", "answers": ["8", "7", "9", "6"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 9 + 3?", "answers": ["11", "12", "10", "14"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 5?", "answers": ["1", "3", "2", "4"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 + 4?", "answers": ["6", "9", "8", "7"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 2?", "answers": ["9", "8", "7", "10"], "correctAnswer": "8" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 1?", "answers": ["3", "2", "4", "5"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 8?", "answers": ["14", "13", "15", "16"], "correctAnswer": "15" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 9 - 3?", "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "4"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 7?", "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "11"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 4?", "answers": ["7", "5", "6", "8"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 2?", "answers": ["9", "11", "10", "12"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 6?", "answers": ["10", "11", "12", "9"], "correctAnswer": "11" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 3?", "answers": ["4", "5", "3", "2"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 + 4?", "answers": ["7", "6", "5", "8"], "correctAnswer": "7" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 9 - 5?", "answers": ["5", "4", "3", "6"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 5?", "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"], "correctAnswer": "7" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 + 6?", "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 3?", "answers": ["4", "3", "5", "6"], "correctAnswer": "4" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 + 9?", "answers": ["8", "10", "9", "11"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 - 5?", "answers": ["4", "3", "2", "5"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 + 6?", "answers": ["7", "8", "9", "10"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 7?", "answers": ["4", "2", "3", "1"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 5?", "answers": ["10", "11", "12", "9"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 3?", "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "11"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 - 6?", "answers": ["2", "1", "3", "0"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 + 5?", "answers": ["9", "10", "8", "7"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 9 - 2?", "answers": ["6", "5", "7", "8"], "correctAnswer": "7" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 8?", "answers": ["10", "9", "11", "8"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 2?", "answers": ["4", "3", "2", "1"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 5?", "answers": ["12", "11", "10", "13"], "correctAnswer": "11" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 2?", "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "7"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 - 3?", "answers": ["2", "1", "3", "0"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 1 + 8?", "answers": ["8", "9", "10", "11"], "correctAnswer": "9" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 9?", "answers": ["2", "0", "1", "3"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 + 4?", "answers": ["11", "12", "13", "14"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 - 2?", "answers": ["2", "1", "3", "0"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 7?", "answers": ["12", "14", "13", "11"], "correctAnswer": "13" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 2 + 4?", "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "8"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 3?", "answers": ["3", "2", "4", "1"], "correctAnswer": "2" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 6?", "answers": ["12", "13", "14", "15"], "correctAnswer": "13" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 3?", "answers": ["6", "7", "8", "9"], "correctAnswer": "7" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 + 8?", "answers": ["9", "10", "11", "12"], "correctAnswer": "11" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 - 1?", "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 7?", "answers": ["11", "12", "13", "10"], "correctAnswer": "12" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 - 5?", "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "0"], "correctAnswer": "1" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 4 + 6?", "answers": ["9", "10", "11", "12"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 7 + 3?", "answers": ["10", "11", "12", "13"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 + 9?", "answers": ["12", "13", "14", "15"], "correctAnswer": "14" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 8 - 3?", "answers": ["6", "4", "5", "3"], "correctAnswer": "5" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 6 + 4?", "answers": ["11", "9", "10", "12"], "correctAnswer": "10" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 3 + 3?", "answers": ["6", "5", "7", "4"], "correctAnswer": "6" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 5 - 2?", "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "correctAnswer": "3" },
    { "grade": 1, "subject": "Math", "question": "What is 10 - 5?", "answers": ["5", "4", "6", "7"], "correctAnswer": "5" }
  ]
}